{
  "movies": [
    {
		"id": 0,
		"question" : "A Shared collection of logical related data (and a description of this data), designed to meet the information needs of an organization",
		"a": "DDL" ,
		"b": "DML" ,
		"c": "Database" ,
		"d": "Transaction" ,
		"answer": "c"
	},
	{
		"id": 1,
		"question": "Greatest potential for Performance improvment is in? (where quesries originate), not the database (which stores the data) or the physical enviroment where the database resides",
		"a": "System",
		"b": "Application",
		"c": "Database",
		"d": "All of the above",
		"answer": "b"
  	}
	
  ],
  "211": [
	  {
		"id": 0,
		"question": "What is the advantages of JSX over the original React language",
		"a": "less code generally means less chance for errors! and code is easier to read",
		"b": "fast performance",
		"c": "easy to undestand",
		"d": "All of the above",
		"answer": "a"
	},
	{
		"id": 1,
		"question": "To render more than one element what do you need to wrap in?",
		"a": "JSX",
		"b": "ReactDOM.render",
		"c": "React.createElement",
		"d": "React.Fragment",
		"answer": "d"
	},
	{
		"id": 2,
		"question": "How many can ReactDOM.render() element can accept?",
		"a": "As many as you need",
		"b": "one",
		"c": "three",
		"d": "only a few",
		"answer": "b"
	},
	{
		"id": 3,
		"question": "Any JS Expression can be embedded in JSX by surrounding it with what?",
		"a": "curly braces {}",
		"b": "square braket []",
		"c": "tick `",
		"d": "round bracket ()",
		"answer": "a"
	},
	{
		"id": 4,
		"question": "How  can you comment in JSX code?",
		"a": "# likethis",
		"b": "// comment",
		"c": "{/* comment */}",
		"d": "{//comment}",
		"answer": "c"
	},
	{
		"id": 5,
		"question": "How can JSX execute in the browsers?",
		"a": "Because its a javascript is its normal for it to execute",
		"b": "Babel is a transpiler for JSX takes any JSX and transpiles it to JS",
		"c": "Babel is the compiler for Browser",
		"d": "Javascript has a library to compile the JSX automatically",
		"answer": "b"
	},
	{
		"id": 6,
		"question": "What is React Component?",
		"a": "It's a React Component where you can create e.g., Function",
		"b": "Multi-DOM",
		"c": "Props",
		"d": "Web Dev",
		"answer": "a"
	},
	{
		"id": 7,
		"question": "____ Components allow you to encapsulate several DOM elements",
		"a": "use State class",
		"b": "Hook State",
		"c": "React.createElement",
		"d": "React Function",
		"answer": "d"
	},
	{
		"id": 8,
		"question": "Function Components are _______ - they don't store any kind of state   they are the most basic React Component",
		"a": "React Element",
		"b": "Dom",
		"c": "Props",
		"d": "Stateless",
		"answer": "d"
	},
	{
		"id": 9,
		"question": "_____ is the object that is made up of JSX attributes (data) passed in on creation of the Component",
		"a": "Dom",
		"b": "React",
		"c": "Props",
		"d": "React State Class",
		"answer": "c"
	},
	{
		"id": 10,
		"question": "React elements can be either ______ or _______",
		"a": "Dom elements or React Components",
		"b": "Function or Variable",
		"c": "Parent or child",
		"d": "All of the above",
		"answer": "a"
	}
	
  ]
}
